sellphones.pk 2017-05-28

# Sellphones.pk - Privacy Policy

**SellPhones.PK** is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its interactive products and services. Through the Internet, our primary goal is to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers and site visitors just looking for information. 

* * *

> **Disclosre**  
>  We do not disclose information about your individual visits with any other company. Information such as your name, address, email address, telephone numbers, etc. are not mis used by **SellPhones.PK** or any of its partners, We do collect information from website submissions and for newsletters purposes. This information is limited to your email which is used to confirm submissions or notify of changes to listings that may affect a website within our directory. **SellPhones.PK** may share such information in response to any legal processes, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. Otherwise, this information is kept in secure confidentiality. 

> **Information**  
>  The purpose of storing any personal information you may provide us when you visit our site or fill out any **SellPhones.PK** forms, is to enable **SellPhones.PK** to maintain communication with you. We will not sell, share, or give this information to any other company. **SellPhones.PK** will only disclose user information to the proper authorities, when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
> 
> * * *
> 
> If we use cookies, it is only to help us serve you better. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. **SellPhones.PK** does not control these cookies or any other applications or tracking controls from other advertisers or partners of **SellPhones.PK**.
> 
> * * *
> 
> Remember that whenever you give out personal information on the Internet, that information can be intercepted in transit. While we strive to protect any personal information in our possession, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk except for on our secure pages. **SellPhones.PK** will only receive credit card / Debit card information through different payment gateways over a SSL (secure encrypted) connection.
> 
> * * *
> 
> By using this site, you agree to the **SellPhones.PK** Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the **SellPhones.PK** site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
> 
> * * *
> 
> if you have any question regarding our privacy policies do not hesitate to send email us at **contact[at]sellphones.pk**
